FIRST NAME: Mustafa LAST NAME: Sharif Asl

Your Cell Phone (+98)9190788594 •Your Email Address: mostafasharif8@gmail.com • City :Tehran • Personalized LinkedIn Link: mostafa-sharif-3173471b9 • Birth Date :July 02, 1997

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Write 3-5 lines in a paragraph format where you explain your professional accomplishments. It is recommended that you summarize your experience, achievements, education, leadership, and expertise in this paragraph. Try to add top keywords in the summary.

Hello Sir I'm Mustafa Sharif Asl Since I can remember I was trying to be a successful guy in my whole life! So Now I have this skills: HTML5 CSS3 & SCSS /Java script & JQuery/ Word press /Bootstrap5 & responsive Design/Introductions of SEO & React.

I have 2.5 year experience with personal & company clients and now I want to work with great companies in uropa.

Thanks for your time

Core Competencies and Skills:

- HTML5 CSS3 & SCSS
- Java script & JQuery/
- Word press
- Bootstrap5 & responsive Design
- Introductions of SEO
- React
- CREATIVITY AND TEAM WORK

WORK EXPERIENCE

Salesmanship

July 2016 - 2017

Gold Sales

That was the first experience of a great work, really it was so hard for me all the time but always I say THANKS GOD for all of that.

Trade and Export Expert

Jun 2018 - Dec 2019

Export Expert

In this time of my life I was trying so hard to learn Arabic because we were working only with Arab countries and really I have tried hard to speak well as well & here we go!

Word press Designer

Feb 2020 - Present

Front-End Developer & word press Web Designer(FreeLancer)

In Fact this time was not the first time witch I have meet word press.

Sure, I was have some experience & Designing some sites for my Friends, But technically this time I was so deep in it and I have Done Some websites for Iraq & Syria & Russia & Germany For my Clients

After That I was Curious so I have decided to learn coding

EDUCATION

Associate of English literature

Jun 2019 - 2021

English literature University: Azad university central Tehran branch

In this time of my life i have learned to speak great & learn English & steel I am learning.

ADDITIONAL

Personal/Other:

- Something you started that shows you're an entrepreneur / Team Player / Charity / Community Service
 - o Impressive, interesting, unique information on this activity | What did you accomplish?
 - One day I started a business: The name was Asefrey, It was so hard for me to start it alone but at the end I failed in this business!! It was so hard for me, I was depressed for a long time because I put all my financial and spiritual strength for this business, but after a while I stood up and told him to get up, man.

I am a complete failure and of course a worker I will not lose my spirit anymore!

- Interests: Front-end developer
- Languages: English (Advance) & Arabic(Advance) & Persian (Native)
- My website: https://www.sharifasl.com